# Nur Uj Jaman Khan

Dhaka, Bangladesh



nurujjaman1310@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/jamankhan1310

#### Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Computer Numerical Control (CNC), Enterprise Software, Enterprise Technology Sales, Software Development, and Web Applications. Strong engineering professional with a Associate's degree focused in Mechanical Engineering from Institute of Engineers Bangladesh.

#### **Experience**



#### python and Artificial Intelligence Developer

Upwork

Jun 2021 - Present (2 years 3 months)

Working as a freelance computer vision, artificial intelligence, neural network, NLP, GAN experts

# Computer Programmer

Fiverr

Sep 2020 - Present (3 years)

Working as a freelance software engineer

# Software Engineer

Singularity Infotech

May 2019 - Present (4 years 4 months)

## Engineer

RAEDIAL ARCHITECTS & ENGINEERS

# Scientific Researcher

Jashore University of Science and Technology

Mar 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months)

## Co-Founder

NiSA Engineering Works & Associates

Jul 2020 - Present (3 years 2 months)

## **Javascript Developer**

Aspro Soft Ltd

Oct 2018 - Present (4 years 11 months)

## Web Developer Full Stack

Raedial Architectures and Engineers Feb 2018 - Present (5 years 7 months)

## Python Developer

Singular IT Jul 2020 - Jun 2021 (1 year)

#### **Education**

## Institute of Engineers Bangladesh

Associate's degree, Mechanical Engineering 2019 - 2023

Graduation in Mechanical Engineering Degree Pursuing which is equivalent 4 Years degree of Bachelor of Science in Engineering.

# Jashore University of Science and Technology

Master of Engineering - MEng, Electrical and Electronics Engineering 2020 - 2022

## Jashore University of Science and Technology

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science and Engineering 2016 - 2020

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- **Enterprise Computing** IBM
- Energy Production Distribution and Safety University at Buffalo BZPRFRJYFEV3
- Digital Manufacturing & Design Technology University at Buffalo UPAVMTBXZBWC
- **Developing Industrial Internet of Things** University of Colorado Boulder JZTJQ993HRSY
- Python for Everybody University of Michigan 6ETFQ8G3488Q
- DeepLearning.Al TensorFlow Developer DeepLearning.Al 4RLQ9BDQB66J

- Google IT Automation Professional Certificate Google
  Google IT Automation with Python
- Introduction to Enterprise Computing IBM
- Autodesk Certified Credential in CAD/CAM for Manufacturing Autodesk

#### **Skills**

Deep Learning • Analytical Skills • Computer Vision • C++ • Machine Learning • Artificial Intelligence (AI) • Engineering • Computing • Enterprise Technology Sales • Software Development